{
  "admin": [
    {
      "admin_name": "admin",
      "admin_password": "4321"
    }
  ],
  "subject": [
    {
      "subject_name": "Maths",
      "id": 1
    },
    {
      "subject_name": "java",
      "id": 2
    },
    {
      "subject_name": "dbms",
      "id": 3
    },
    {
      "subject_name": "os",
      "id": 4
    }
  ],
  "Exam": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "exam_name": "Maths",
      "exam_desc": "This is Math Exam",
      "exam_date": "17-9-2021 17:49:39",
      "exam_marks": "5",
      "exam_totalQuestion": "5",
      "exam_passMarks": "3",
      "exam_level": "Easy"
    },
    {
      "exam_name": "java",
      "exam_desc": "java exam",
      "exam_level": "easy",
      "exam_passMarks": "3",
      "exam_totalQuestion": "5",
      "exam_marks": "5",
      "exam_date": "29-11-2023 23:5:34",
      "id": 2
    },
    {
      "exam_name": "dbms",
      "exam_desc": "this is database management system exam.",
      "exam_level": "easy",
      "exam_passMarks": "2",
      "exam_totalQuestion": "4",
      "exam_marks": "4",
      "exam_date": "9-12-2023 12:0:31",
      "id": 3
    },
    {
      "exam_name": "os",
      "exam_desc": "os",
      "exam_level": "easy",
      "exam_passMarks": "2",
      "exam_totalQuestion": "3",
      "exam_marks": "6",
      "exam_date": "9-12-2023 12:32:15",
      "id": 4
    }
  ],
  "Question": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "question_name": "10-5 ?",
      "option_one": "3",
      "option_two": "1",
      "option_three": "2",
      "option_four": "5",
      "question_answer": "5",
      "exam_id": 1,
      "subject_name": "Maths"
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "question_name": "10+5 ?",
      "option_one": "3",
      "option_two": "1",
      "option_three": "4",
      "option_four": "15",
      "question_answer": "15",
      "exam_id": 1,
      "subject_name": "Maths"
    },
    {
      "question_name": "10*5",
      "option_one": "10",
      "option_two": "5",
      "option_three": "50",
      "option_four": "2",
      "question_answer": "50",
      "exam_id": "1",
      "subject_name": "Maths",
      "id": 3
    },
    {
      "question_name": "110-10 ?",
      "option_one": "110",
      "option_two": "100",
      "option_three": "10",
      "option_four": "1",
      "question_answer": "100",
      "exam_id": "1",
      "subject_name": "Maths",
      "id": 4
    },
    {
      "question_name": "10/2 = ?",
      "option_one": "1",
      "option_two": "5",
      "option_three": "10",
      "option_four": "7",
      "question_answer": "5",
      "exam_id": "1",
      "subject_name": "Maths",
      "id": 5
    },
    {
      "question_name": "Number of primitive data types in Java are?",
      "option_one": "6",
      "option_two": "7",
      "option_three": "8",
      "option_four": "9",
      "question_answer": "8",
      "exam_id": "2",
      "subject_name": "java",
      "id": 6
    },
    {
      "question_name": "What is the size of float and double in java?",
      "option_one": "32 and 64",
      "option_two": "32 and 32",
      "option_three": "64 and 64",
      "option_four": "none",
      "question_answer": "32 and 64",
      "exam_id": "2",
      "subject_name": "java",
      "id": 7
    },
    {
      "question_name": "Automatic type conversion is possible in which of the possible cases?",
      "option_one": "int to long",
      "option_two": "byte to int",
      "option_three": " long to int",
      "option_four": "short to int",
      "question_answer": "int to long",
      "exam_id": "2",
      "subject_name": "java",
      "id": 8
    },
    {
      "question_name": " Arrays in java are-",
      "option_one": "object references",
      "option_two": "object",
      "option_three": "primitive datatypes",
      "option_four": "none",
      "question_answer": "object",
      "exam_id": "2",
      "subject_name": "java",
      "id": 9
    },
    {
      "question_name": "When is the object created with new keyword",
      "option_one": "at run time",
      "option_two": "at compile time",
      "option_three": "depends on code",
      "option_four": "all of the above",
      "question_answer": "at run time",
      "exam_id": "2",
      "subject_name": "java",
      "id": 10
    },
    {
      "question_name": "which of the following is used for performing tasks like creating the structure of relations?",
      "option_one": "DML",
      "option_two": "query",
      "option_three": "relational schema",
      "option_four": "DDL",
      "question_answer": "DDL",
      "exam_id": "3",
      "subject_name": "DBMS",
      "id": 11
    },
    {
      "question_name": "fullform of dbms ?",
      "option_one": "database management system",
      "option_two": "database manage system",
      "option_three": "database management schema",
      "option_four": "data management schema",
      "question_answer": "database management system",
      "exam_id": "3",
      "subject_name": "DBMS",
      "id": 12
    },
    {
      "question_name": "what is DBMS?",
      "option_one": "collection of queries",
      "option_two": "high level language",
      "option_three": "programming language",
      "option_four": "store , modifies and retrieves data",
      "question_answer": "store , modifies and retrieves data",
      "exam_id": "3",
      "subject_name": "DBMS",
      "id": 13
    },
    {
      "question_name": "who created DBMS?",
      "option_one": "edgar frank",
      "option_two": "charles",
      "option_three": "charles bachman",
      "option_four": "sharon B codd",
      "question_answer": "charles bachman",
      "exam_id": "3",
      "subject_name": "DBMS",
      "id": 14
    },
    {
      "question_name": "which of the following is not an operating system?",
      "option_one": "DOS",
      "option_two": "oracle",
      "option_three": "linux",
      "option_four": "windows",
      "question_answer": "oracle",
      "exam_id": "4",
      "subject_name": "os",
      "id": 15
    },
    {
      "question_name": " What is the maximum length of the filename in DOS?",
      "option_one": "10",
      "option_two": "12",
      "option_three": "13",
      "option_four": "8",
      "question_answer": "8",
      "exam_id": "4",
      "subject_name": "os",
      "id": 16
    },
    {
      "question_name": "When was the first operating system developed?",
      "option_one": "1900",
      "option_two": "2000",
      "option_three": "1950",
      "option_four": "1999",
      "question_answer": "1950",
      "exam_id": "4",
      "subject_name": "os",
      "id": 17
    }
  ],
  "Result": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "result_status": "Pass",
      "result_score": "3",
      "user_email": "ram@gmail.com",
      "exam_date": "12-23-12",
      "exam_name": "Maths",
      "total_marks": "5",
      "exam_id": "1",
      "total_Question": "5"
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "result_status": "Pass",
      "result_score": "3",
      "user_email": "ram@gmail.com",
      "exam_date": "12-23-12",
      "exam_name": "Maths",
      "total_marks": "5",
      "exam_id": "1",
      "total_Question": "5"
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "result_status": "Pass",
      "result_score": "3",
      "user_email": "shiv@gmail.com",
      "exam_date": "12-23-12",
      "exam_name": "Maths",
      "total_marks": "5",
      "exam_id": "1",
      "total_Question": "5"
    },
    {
      "result_status": "Pass",
      "result_score": 3,
      "user_email": "ram@gmail.com",
      "exam_date": "18-9-2021 20:49:39",
      "exam_name": "Maths",
      "total_marks": "5",
      "exam_id": "1",
      "total_Question": "5",
      "id": 4
    },
    {
      "result_status": "Pass",
      "result_score": 4,
      "user_email": "vishnu@gmail.com",
      "exam_date": "19-9-2021 15:11:27",
      "exam_name": "Maths",
      "total_marks": "5",
      "exam_id": "1",
      "total_Question": "5",
      "id": 5
    },
    {
      "result_status": "Pass",
      "result_score": 4,
      "user_email": "agni@gmail.com",
      "exam_date": "19-9-2021 15:20:37",
      "exam_name": "Maths",
      "total_marks": "5",
      "exam_id": "1",
      "total_Question": "5",
      "id": 6
    },
    {
      "result_status": "Pass",
      "result_score": 5,
      "user_email": "ram@gmail.com",
      "exam_date": "29-11-2023 23:2:11",
      "exam_name": "Maths",
      "total_marks": "5",
      "exam_id": "1",
      "total_Question": "5",
      "id": 7
    },
    {
      "result_status": "Pass",
      "result_score": 4,
      "user_email": "ram@gmail.com",
      "exam_date": "29-11-2023 23:13:34",
      "exam_name": "Maths",
      "total_marks": "5",
      "exam_id": "2",
      "total_Question": "5",
      "id": 8
    },
    {
      "result_status": "Pass",
      "result_score": 4,
      "user_email": "ram@gmail.com",
      "exam_date": "9-12-2023 11:54:6",
      "exam_name": "Maths",
      "total_marks": "5",
      "exam_id": "2",
      "total_Question": "5",
      "id": 9
    },
    {
      "result_status": "Pass",
      "result_score": 4,
      "user_email": "ishika@gmail.com",
      "exam_date": "9-12-2023 11:58:37",
      "exam_name": "Maths",
      "total_marks": "5",
      "exam_id": "2",
      "total_Question": "5",
      "id": 10
    },
    {
      "result_status": "Fail",
      "result_score": 2,
      "user_email": "ishika@gmail.com",
      "exam_date": "9-12-2023 12:20:7",
      "exam_name": "Maths",
      "total_marks": "5",
      "exam_id": "2",
      "total_Question": "5",
      "id": 11
    },
    {
      "result_status": "Fail",
      "result_score": 0,
      "user_email": "ishika@gmail.com",
      "exam_date": "9-12-2023 12:42:1",
      "exam_name": "Maths",
      "total_marks": "5",
      "exam_id": "3",
      "total_Question": "5",
      "id": 12
    },
    {
      "result_status": "Fail",
      "result_score": 1,
      "user_email": "ishika@gmail.com",
      "exam_date": "9-12-2023 12:43:29",
      "exam_name": "Maths",
      "total_marks": "5",
      "exam_id": "3",
      "total_Question": "5",
      "id": 13
    },
    {
      "result_status": "Pass",
      "result_score": 3,
      "user_email": "ishika@gmail.com",
      "exam_date": "9-12-2023 12:50:51",
      "exam_name": "Maths",
      "total_marks": "5",
      "exam_id": "5",
      "total_Question": "5",
      "id": 14
    }
  ],
  "user": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "user_name": "ishika",
      "user_email": "ishika@gmail.com",
      "user_password": "ish@1234"
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "user_name": "shiv",
      "user_email": "shiv@gmail.com",
      "user_password": "1234"
    },
    {
      "user_name": "Vishnu",
      "user_email": "vishnu@gmail.com",
      "user_password": "123",
      "id": 3
    },
    {
      "user_name": "Agni",
      "user_email": "agni@gmail.com",
      "user_password": "123",
      "id": 4
    },
    {
      "user_name": "isha thapliyal",
      "user_email": "ishathapliyal@gmail.com",
      "user_password": "ishathapliyal",
      "id": 5
    },
    {
      "user_name": "ish",
      "user_email": "ish@gmail.com",
      "user_password": "ish1234",
      "id": 6
    }
  ]
}